Cooperative Recreation Service collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Cooperative Recreation Service collection 1924-2011
AFC 2016/051
29,950 items; 107 containers; 42.5 linear feet.
sound recordings: 2 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
sound recordings: 1 sound disc: analog, 45 rpm; 7 in.
manuscripts: 42 linear ft.
manuscripts: 29,947 items.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of manuscripts and publications comprising the records of the Cooperative Recreation Service (Delaware, Ohio) and additions by subsequent owners, including World Around Songs, a division of Compassion Books, Inc. Includes correspondence with authors and collectors of songs and games; copyright and permission files; most of the original publications of the CRS; folders of individual folk dance and folk song titles pasted-up for publication; and master negatives of songs and games for publication. Genres include American and International folk songs, Contemporary songs, Humorous songs, Work songs, Carols, Rounds, Spirituals, Hymns, and Canons. Popular titles published by the Cooperative Recreation Service include: Handy play party book (1940, 1982); Work and sing: an international songbook (1944, 1948); Look away: 50 Negro folk songs (1960, 1963); Songs of all time (1946, 1957); African songs (1958); Songs of the wigwam (1955); Little book of carols (1960); One tune more: songs of America (1961); and Handy folklore (1955); among many others.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Greene, Bruce, 1951-; Rohrbough, Lynn--Correspondence.
Organizations
Cooperative Recreation Service (Delaware, Ohio)
Subjects
Folk dancing.; Folk drama.; Folk songs.; Folklore.; Games.; Play-party.; Puzzles.; Riddles.; Singing games.; Tales.; Work songs.
Places
Burnsville (Anson County, N.C.) Production place.; Delaware (Ohio) Production place.
Form/Genre
Carols.; Correspondence.; Folk songs.; Hymns.; Kits (sets); Manuscripts for publication.; Manuscripts.; Posters.; Scores.; Songbooks.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: series 1. Custom songbooks and "Kit" recreation publications; series 2. Song sheets; series 3. Production files/custom songbook files; series 4. Song indexes and copyright research.
Arrangement is primarily alphabetical by title.
Acquisition
Bruce Greene, World Around Songs; 2016.
Separated Materials
57 publications have been removed from the collection. A portion of these publications have been transferred to the Library of Congress' General Collections and Music Division. A smaller portion have been deaccessioned according to the Library of Congress' collection policies.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research; access to collection materials may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Biographical Note
The Cooperative Recreation Service was formed as a publishing and distribution center for kits, songbooks, and pamphlets of folk games and songs from the United States and around the world by Lynn Rohrbough and his wife Katherine Ferris Rohrbough in the late 1920s. The Rorhboughs first collected songs and dances while traveling as recreation leaders in churches throughout North America in the 1930s. The publications were sold and distributed to youth agencies and church groups in the United States and internationally.
Scope and Content
Collection of manuscripts and publications comprising the records of the Cooperative Recreation Service (Delaware, Ohio) and additions by subsequent owners, including World Around Songs, a division of Compassion Books, Inc. Includes correspondence with authors and collectors of songs and games; copyright and permission files; most of the original publications of the CRS; folders of individual folk dance and folk song titles pasted-up for publication; and master negatives of songs and games for publication. Genres include American and International folk songs, Contemporary songs, Humorous songs, Work songs, Carols, Rounds, Spirituals, Hymns, and Canons. Popular titles published by the Cooperative Recreation Service include: Handy play party book (1940, 1982); Work and sing: an international songbook (1944, 1948); Look away: 50 Negro folk songs (1960, 1963); Songs of all time (1946, 1957); African songs (1958); Songs of the wigwam (1955); Little book of carols (1960); One tune more: songs of America (1961); and Handy folklore (1955); among many others.
Container List
- Series 1. Custom songbooks, "Kit" recreation publications, and selected published materials, ca. 1924-2005
  This series includes the range of custom songbooks and recreation publications published during the lifespan of Cooperative Recreation Service and including some publications from the transition to World Around Songs publishing company. Arranged alphabetically, each box including a range of songbooks.
  - A-Po-Keep--Sing through Brothers Sing Out, undated, 75 items (Box 1)
  - Buckeye Ballads--Come, Let Us Sing!, undated, 77 items (Box 2)
  - Come, Let's Sing!--Fellowship in Song, undated, 80 items (Box 3)
  - Fellowship Song Book--Girl Scouts Song Book, undated, 75 items (Box 4)
  - Gloria '67--Holston Sings, undated, 75 items (Box 5)
  - Home Land Songs--Joyfully We Sing II, undated, 82 items (Box 6)
  - Joyfully We Sing V--Let Us Sing Together, undated, 73 items (Box 7)
  - Let Us Sing Together--MIA Let's Sing No. 2, undated, 72 items (Box 8)
  - Miami County Sings--Nochebuena Y Navidad, undated, 70 items (Box 9)
  - North Indiana Sings--Peninsula Conference Fellowship Songs, undated, 72 items (Box 10)
  - Peninsula Conference Fellowship Songs--A Sampler of Friendly Folk Songs, undated, 82 items (Box 11)
  - A Sampler of Friendly Folk Songs--Sing All Day, undated, 72 items (Box 12)
  - Sing Along--Sing with 4-H, undated, 76 items (Box 13)
  - Sing With FHA--Singorama, undated, 67 items (Box 14)
  - Social Renascence Song Book--Songs From Here and There, undated, 78 items (Box 15)
  - Songs from the Heart of Gambier Island...Camp Arteban--Songs to Keep, undated, 65 items (Box 16)
  - Songs to Keep--Tent and Trail Songs, undated, 69 items (Box 17)
  - Tent and Trail Songs--Wesley Woods Methodist Camp Sings, undated, 80 items (Box 18)
  - Wesleyan Service Guild--Youth United in the Western Pennsylvania Methodist Youth Fellowship, undated, 62 items (Box 19)
  - "Handy=Kit": Recreation Quarterly No. 1 Winter 1925--The Recreation "Kit" 27. Vol. VII, No. 3, ca. 1924-1932, 78 items (Box 20)
  - "Kit" 28 Vol. VII, No. 4-Kit Z--Romancing: Folk Lore on Courtship, ca. 1932-1940, 93 items (Box 21)
  - Selected published materials, ca. 1931-2004, 29 items (Box 103-104)
    Published songbooks, both by World Around Songs, as well as by other publishers that served as research and reference materials for the publishing company. List of publications and bibliographic information included in Published materials.
- Series 2. Song Sheets, undated
  Individual song sheet cards and song master negatives used for research and publication of custom songbooks. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Subseries 1. Song Master sheets, undated
    - A Donde, A Donde-Animal Song, undated (Box 22)
    - Anne Marieken--The Bells of Old Harlem, undated (Box 23)
    - Beneath the Cross of Jesus-Burmese Blessing, undated (Box 24)
    - Burn, Fire, Burn-Christ is Our Victory, undated (Box 25)
    - Christ is Risen--Country Life, undated (Box 26)
    - Courage to Be--Donkey Riding, undated (Box 27)
    - Don't Fence Me In--(Farewell to Thee) Aloha Oe, undated (Box 28)
    - Farmer Boy--French Counting Song, undated (Box 29)
    - Fried Ham--Go Tell Aunt Rhody, undated (Box 30)
    - Go Tell Everyone--Grandfather's Clock, undated (Box 31)
    - Grandma Grunts--Heaven Flows (Der Himmel Geht), undated (Box 32)
    - Heaven is a Wonderful Place--Hurry, Little Donkey, undated (Box 33)
    - Hush Little Baby--Illkly Moor, undated (Box 34)
    - I'm a 4-H Member--Jesus' Birthday Dawning, undated (Box 35)
    - Jesus Calls Us--Leaning in the Everlasting Arms, undated (Box 36)
    - Leatherwing Bat--Littlest Worm, undated (Box 37)
    - Live Love--Manuel Road, undated (Box 38)
    - Many Bags--My Aunt Greet, undated (Box 39)
    - My Baby Chicken--Now Let Every Tongue Adore Thee, undated (Box 40)
    - Now Let Us Sing--O Worship the King, undated (Box 41)
    - O Yepo--Our Father Thy Dear Name Doth Show, undated (Box 42)
    - Our Father, Who Art in Heaven--Plowing Song, undated (Box 43)
    - Po, Po, Po--Rejoice, Ye Pure in Heart (Dad Gracias y Hoy Cantad), undated (Box 44)
    - Remember--Savior, Hear Us, undated (Box 45)
    - Savior, Like a Shepherd Lead Us--The Sloop John B, undated (Box 46)
    - Slumber Boat (Baby's Boat)--Stay With Me, undated (Box 47)
    - Steal Away--There Was a Lawyer, undated (Box 48)
    - There Was a Little Sandy Girl--Tumbalalaicka, undated (Box 49)
    - Tuoll'on Mun Kultani--We Give Thanks, undated (Box 50)
    - We Have Christ in Our Life--When Oscar Went a Yodeling, undated (Box 51)
    - When Spring Returns--Ye Shepherds Leave Your Flocks, undated (Box 52)
    - Year of Jubilo--Zum Gali Gali; Folk Dance files, A&D--Portland Fancy, undated (Box 53)
      Includes Song Master sheets and Folk Dance files.
    - Rheinlaender for Three--Your Best Liking, undated (Box 54)
      Folk Dance files.
  - Subseries 2. Song Master negatives, undated
    Song master negatives compiled for Cooperative Recreation Service publications.
    - A Blessing--Chester, undated (Box 55)
    - Chestnut Tree--Forest Gypsy, undated (Box 56)
    - Forth in Thy Name, O Lord, I Go--I Will Sing the Wondrous Story, undated (Box 57)
    - Ice Wagon Song--Lord, Lord, undated (Box 58)
    - Lord, Lord, Lord--Oh What a Beautiful Morning, undated (Box 59)
    - Oh, Wohel--Sister Sally, undated (Box 60)
    - Six Little Ducks--Weihnachts Jodler, undated (Box 61)
    - Welcome Table--Zum Gali Gali, undated (Box 62)
    - Tent and Trail Songs, American Camping Associations, North Martinsville, Indiana, undated, AFC 2016/051: OS01-GR01; 1 print: color, 13 1/4 x 13 1/16 in.
      Sketches and negative cutouts used to print songbooks.
    - Tent and Trail Songs, undated, AFC 2016/051: OS01-GR02; 1 print: color, 13 3/8 x 12 3/4 in.
    - Life on the H2O, undated, AFC 2016/051: OS01-GR03; 1 print: color, 20 5/8 x 25 1/4 in.
    - Life on the H2O, undated, AFC 2016/051: OS01-GR04; black and white, 20 3/4 x 24 3/4 in.
    - [Camping songs from Tent and Trail], undated, AFC 2016/051: OS01-GR05; color, 23 1/8 x 26 9/16 in.
  - Subseries 3. Duplicate song sheets, undated
    - Away in a Manger--Foxlease Vesper, undated (Box 63)
    - Fray Martin--Mow the Hay, undated (Box 64)
    - Mugsi, Mugsi--Try the Riddle, undated (Box 65)
    - Tuku Tuku Iampaitani (Calling the Flock)--Youth Undaunted, undated (Box 66)
- Series 3. Production Files/Custom Songbook Files, ca. 1932-2008
  Manuscripts associated with the publication of Cooperative Recreation Service and World Around Songs songbooks. Includes correspondence with organizations from geographic areas that songbooks are about, as well as copyright, licensing, permissions, and other publishing research. Documentation of research associated with the songbooks, including related song lists, song indexes, and notes.
  - African material, ca. 1958-1995 (Box-folder 67/1)
    Includes African Songs custom songbook, as well as related planning materials.
  - African songs and permissions, ca. 1958-1995 (Box-folder 67/2)
  - American Camping Association (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1978-1986 (Box-folder 67/3)
  - American Camping Association (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1978-1986 (Box-folder 67/4)
  - American Camping Association (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1965-1977 (Box-folder 67/5)
  - American Camping Association (ACA) Sing, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 67/6)
  - American Camping Association (ACA) Tent and Trail Songs, ca. 1962-1990 (Box-folder 67/7)
    Planning materials and copyright information for Tent and Trail Songs custom songbook.
  - Anchorage School District, ca. 1968-1982 (Box-folder 67/8)
    Correspondence about between Anchorage School District staff and Cooperative Recreation Service (Nancy Cope) about using songs and songbooks.
  - Anderson, Walter, ca. 1947-1970 (Box-folder 67/9)
    Correspondence with Walter Anderson, professor at Antioch College.
  - Audubon Girl Scout correspondence, ca. 1987-1988 (Box-folder 67/10)
  - Austria and Germany, songs, ca. 1955-1965 (Box-folder 68/1)
  - Background material, ca. 1935-1954 (Box-folder 68/2)
    John C. Campbell Folk School, Pine Mountain Settlement School information.
  - Boy Scouts, Ely, Minnesota, ca. 1980 (Box-folder 68/3)
    Correspondence between Boy Scouts of America and World Around Songs (Nancy Cope).
  - Bright School, ca. 1982-1984 (Box-folder 68/4)
    Correspondence between the Bright School and World Around Songs (Nancy Cope) about developing song lists for their custom songbook.
  - Buffalo State College/Virginia Austin, ca. 1978-1985 (Box-folder 68/5)
    Includes "Our Own Songbook: Buffalo State College" custom songbook.
  - Burma-Methodist, ca. 1962-1964 (Box-folder 68/6)
    Includes Burma Sings custom songbook and materials relating to its publication.
  - Cooperative Recreation Service (CRS) songbook lists, undated (Box-folder 68/7)
  - Camp Arteban Society, ca. 1988-1989 (Box-folder 68/8)
    Materials relating to the Camp Arteban songbook.
  - Camp Hebron, correspondence, ca. 1989-1990 (Box-folder 68/9)
    Correspondence relating to the production of the Camp Hebron songbook.
  - Canadian Girls in Training, ca. 1982-1985 (Box-folder 68/10)
    Correspondence relating to a proposed new song collection for the Canadian Girls in Training Association.
  - Cantos, ca. 1959-1969 (Box-folder 68/11)
    Song sheets, song master negatives, and correspondence relating to the Cantos custom songbook.
  - Caribbean Folk Songs and Games, ca. 1962-1967 (Box-folder 68/12)
    Correspondence and song sheets relating to the Caribbean Folk Songs and Games custom songbook.
  - Carol Henry's book (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1985-1990 (Box-folder 69/1)
    Correspondence relating to various songbooks for young children.
  - Carol Henry's book (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1985-1990 (Box-folder 69/2)
  - Carolina Farm Stewardship Association (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1982-1983 (Box-folder 69/3)
    Correspondence about permissions for a songbook of farming and gardening songs for the Carolina Farm Stewardship Association.
  - Carolina Farm Stewardship Association (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1982-1983 (Box-folder 69/4)
    Correspondence, permissions, song sheets, budget notes, and shipping invoices for the Carolina Farm Stewardship Association songbook.
  - Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1985 (Box-folder 69/5)
    Correpondence, permissions, and song sheets relating to the Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet songbook.
  - Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1985 (Box-folder 69/6)
  - China, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 69/7)
    Includes The Pagoda songbook, as well as correspondence and other notes pertaining to the songbook of Chinese folk songs.
  - Come friends..., ca. 1961 (Box-folder 69/8)
    Includes Come Friends... songbook, as well as song master negatives.
  - Cooperative Recreation Service records, ca. 1932-1964 (Box-folder 69/9)
    Includes schedules, reports, and programs for singing and recreation oriented camps and conferences, some of which were led by Lynn Rohrbaugh. Includes correspondence, including a 1940 letter from Olive Dame Campbell.
  - Copyright information, ca. 1984-1985 (Box-folder 70/1)
    Copyright research and correspondence about songs and permissions.
  - Copyright permission requests (folder 1 of 2), ca. 2000-2008 (Box-folder 70/2)
  - Copyright permission requests (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1994-1999 (Box-folder 70/3)
  - Copyright registration, Olcutt Sanders, ca. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 70/4)
  - Copyright registrations (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1952-1981 (Box-folder 70/5)
  - Copyright registrations (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1932-1981 (Box-folder 70/6)
    Includes copyright deposits for custom songbooks.
  - Copyright searches, Copyright Office, ca. 1946-1968 (Box-folder 70/7)
  - Copyright, Herbert L. Smith, ca. 1932-1965 (Box-folder 70/8)
  - Copyrights, unlisted autographs, ca. 1948-1969 (Box-folder 70/9)
  - Copyrights, Cooperative Recreation Service, ca. 1940-1963 (Box-folder 70/10)
  - Correspondence (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1984-1986 (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Correspondence (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 71/1)
  - Correspondence (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1982-1983 (Box-folder 71/2)
  - Count and Capture; Pandi; Others, ca. 1950-1956 (Box-folder 71/3)
    Correspondence and research about games and songs from India, Africa, and Jamaica.
  - Country Life Songs, ca. 1969 (Box-folder 71/4)
    Includes notes and lists of songs.
  - Custom Songbook Prospect, Pilgrim Center, Wisconsin, ca. 2003-2008 (Box-folder 71/5)
    Correspodence and research material for a book project for Pilgrim Center.
  - Directory of Public Domain Sheet Music, ca. 1997-2001 (Box-folder 71/6)
  - Dunsings, ca. 1951-1953 (Box-folder 71/7)
    Includes German folk song sheet music and notes.
  - East Ohio Conference, ca. 1958-1980 (Box-folder 71/8)
    Correspondence and notes about a possible songbook for the East Ohio Conference.
  - Eastern Cooperative Recreation School booklet and research, ca. 1981-1984 (Box-folder 71/9)
  - Easton Girl Scouts (Connecticut), ca. 1985-1987 (Box-folder 72/1)
    Includes custom songbook, correspondence, permissions, and research for Scout Around Songs: Easton Girl Scouts songbook.
  - East-West songs correspondence, ca. 1960-1963 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - East West, ca. 1960-1965, AFC 2016/051: SR02; 5-inch open reel tape
      Includes 43 songs from the East West custom songbook.
  - 88 Top Songs, ca. 1960-1963 (Box-folder 72/3)
    Includes custom songbook, as well as sheet music and notes surrounding the preparation of the book.
  - Larry Eisenberg, copyright, ca. 1992-1993 (Box-folder 72/4)
    Correspondence.
  - Max Exner (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1955-1959 (Box-folder 72/5)
    Correspondence with Max Exner, specialist at Cooperative Extension Service in Agriculture and Home Economics, State of Iowa.
  - Max Exner (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1955-1959 (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Jane Farwell, My Heart Sings, ca. 1966-1981 (Box-folder 72/7)
    Production materials and correspondence for My Heart Sings custom songbook.
  - Financial Statements, ca. 1963-1967 (Box-folder 99/1)
    Cooperative Recreation Service financial statements from Certified Public Accountants Kent and Zerbe.
  - Financial Statements, ca. 1964-1970 (Box-folder 99/2)
  - Financial Statements, ca. 1955-1972 (Box-folder 99/3)
  - Financial issues, World Around Songs, ca. 1983-1986 (Box-folder 72/8)
    Includes correspondence, notes, proposals, invoices, and indexes.
  - Financial records (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1970-1971 (Box-folder 72/9)
    Includes financial statements and tax information.
  - Financial records (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1975-1976 (Box-folder 72/10)
    Includes inventories of custom songbooks and Power of Attorney.
  - Florida United Methodist Camp (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1984 (Box-folder 73/1)
    Includes Sing for the Fun of It custom songbook, as well as notes and correspondence relating to the book's publication.
  - Florida United Methodist Camp (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1984 (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Folklore Village, ca. 1990-1991 (Box-folder 73/3)
    Correspondence and 1 black-and-white photographic print about the Folk Dances for Fun custom songbook by Jane Farwell.
  - For Happy Singing, ca. 1984-1985 (Box-folder 73/4)
    Includes For Happy Singing custom songbook, as well as notes, correspondence, indexes, licenses, and permissions.
  - Four and Twenty Carols, ca. 1963 (Box-folder 73/5)
    Includes Four and Twenty Carols and Holiday Songs custom songbook and correspondence.
  - Friendly Planet (front of drawer), undated (Box-folder 73/6)
    Cards and notes about individual songs.
  - Friendly Planet, 2nd edition, ca. 1986-1987 (Box-folder 73/7)
    Includes two copies of Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet custom songbook, as well as invoices, correspondence, and notes.
  - Friends World Committee, ca. 1987-1992 (Box-folder 73/8)
    Includes Friends Sing in Spirit and in Truth, collected for the Fifth World Conference of Friends, as well as correspondence, invoices, copyrights, and notes.
  - Games, ca. 1927-1960 (Box-folder 74/1)
    Research materials about games.
  - General permissions, ca. 1978-1990 (Box-folder 74/2)
    Correspondence and notes about song permissions.
  - George Mark's Elementary School, ca. 1981 (Box-folder 74/3)
    Invoices, correspondence, notes, and song indexes.
  - Girl Scouts Chalet, ca. 1984-1990 (Box-folder 74/4)
    Permissions, invoices, royalty information, correspondence, and notes.
  - Girl Scouts of Hoosier Capital Council, ca. 2000-2002 (Box-folder 74/5)
    Includes three copies of Girl Scouts of Hoosier Capital Council 90th Anniversary Sing-Along custom songbook, correspondence, notes, and song lists.
  - Good Fellowship Songs Reprint, ca. 1979-1980 (Box-folder 74/6)
    Includes correspondence, permissions, correspondence, and notes.
  - Grace at Table, ca. 1960-1963 (Box-folder 74/7)
    Includes Grace at Table custom songbook, song list, and song sheet negative.
  - Grandma Sings, ca. 1955-1969 (Box-folder 74/8)
    Includes copies and different versions of Grandma Sings custom songbook, correspondence, notes, song sheets, lyrics, and song master negatives.
  - Great Day, Joe Jones, ca. 1964-1969 (Box-folder 74/9)
    Includes Great Day custom songbook, correspondence, and an invoice.
  - Great Valley letters, ca. 1987-1993 (Box-folder 74/10)
    Includes invoices, correspondence, notes, and song lists with the Great Valley Girl Scout Council.
  - Great Valley songbook, ca. 2000-2003 (Box-folder 74/11)
    Notes and quote for printing songbook.
  - Guiana Sings (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1963-1970 (Box-folder 74/12)
    Includes copies and different versions of Guiana Sings custom songbook, correspondence, notes, song master sheet, and song master negatives.
  - Guiana Sings (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1961-1969 (Box-folder 74/13)
    Includes Guiana Sings custom songbook, notes, and correspondence with St. Peter's A.M.E. Church in Guyana, South America.
  - Guiana Sings, ca. 1956-1960, AFC 2016/051: SR01; 1 45rpm vinyl disc
    Recorded Guiana folk songs by Mr. Rafik Khan, Programme Director of the British Guiana United Broadcasting Company.
  - GVGSC (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1984-1988 (Box-folder 75/1)
    Correspondence about a custom songbook for the Great Valley Girl Scout Council in Pennsylvania.
  - GVGSC (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1994-1995 (Box-folder 75/2)
    Correspondence about the reprint of the custom songbook for the Great Valley Girl Scout Council in Pennsylvania.
  - Hulawasa, ca. 1988 (Box-folder 75/3)
    Includes correspondence, and copyright and royalty information.
  - Karen Hamilton, ca. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 75/4)
    Correspondence, invoices, and songbook drafts for Sing a Song & Clap a Song All Year Long custom songbook.
  - Happiness permissions, ca. 1978-1979 (Box-folder 75/5)
    Correspondence, permissions, invoices, and notes about Happiness is a Song custom songbook.
  - Happy Days, ca. 1979 (Box-folder 75/6)
    Permissions for Happy Days custom songbook.
  - Happy Meeting, Czechoslovakia, ca. 1954-1972 (Box-folder 75/7)
    Draft of Happy Meeting: Folk Songs from Czechoslovakia custom songbook.